BUSINESS SYSTEM ANALYST



Versatile Support Specialist skilled handling data, technical issues and personnel support tasks. Self-motivated and attentive with good interpersonal and problem-solving abilities.

Offering 5 years of experience in Business System Analyst.

Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals. Hardworking and passionate job seeker with strong organizational skills eager to secure entry-level analyst position in a competitive environment.





WORK HISTORY

2019-09 - PRESENT

Senior Business Analyst

MASTERCARD, WARSAW

- Responsible for all aspects of operations support for existing customers, including process, business and technical consultation, accountable for developing and maintaining customer support guidelines, metrics and tools
- Collects customer feedback and market intelligence and shares findings with partners in Technology, Product and Customer Delivery
- Reviews customer issues logs, proposes initial enhancements and assists in problem resolution, including escalating advanced issues
- Creating business and system analysis in cooperation with business and IT representatives
- Analyses, troubleshoots, and pulls data to solve customer inquiries; uses a combination of available tools and knowledge
- Reporting work progress and managing project documentation

2017-06 - 2019-08

Business System Analyst

HUAWEI, WARSAW

- Customer support at the highest level, based on Huawei's standards for the latest and flagship smartphones, tablets, computers, routers and modems
- Providing the highest level of expertise and customer guidance for using Huawei devices
- Troubleshoot hardware issues, collaborate with customers, advise on the use of technology used in a product to achieve business goals

EDUCATION

2009-09 - 2015-06

International Relations, Master degree

CARDINAL STEFAN WYSZYNSKI UNIVERSITY, WARSAW

SKILLS

Managing customer relationships, technical issue resolution and troubleshooting, customer service standards, critical thinking;

LANGUAGES

■ Languages: English C1; Polish, Russian and Ukranian C2